<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
- phpMyAdmin XML Dump
- version 4.4.15.10
- https://www.phpmyadmin.net
-
- Host: localhost
- Generation Time: Sep 13, 2019 at 11:22 PM
- Server version: 5.5.60-MariaDB
- PHP Version: 5.4.16
-->

<pma_xml_export version="1.0" xmlns:pma="https://www.phpmyadmin.net/some_doc_url/">
    <!--
    - Structure schemas
    -->
    <pma:structure_schemas>
        <pma:database name="sql1800367" collation="latin1_swedish_ci" charset="latin1">
            <pma:table name="basketball_teams_website">
                CREATE TABLE `basketball_teams_website` (
                  `team_name` varchar(100) NOT NULL,
                  `team_description` varchar(22222) NOT NULL,
                  `image_link` varchar(100) NOT NULL
                ) ENGINE=InnoDB DEFAULT CHARSET=latin1;
            </pma:table>
        </pma:database>
    </pma:structure_schemas>

    <!--
    - Database: 'sql1800367'
    -->
    <database name="sql1800367">
        <!-- Table basketball_teams_website -->
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">New York Knicks</column>
            <column name="team_description">The New York Knickerbockers, more commonly referred to as the Knicks, are an American professional basketball team based in the New York City borough of Manhattan.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/new_york_knicks.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Miami Heat</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Miami Heat are an American professional basketball team based in Miami, Florida. The Heat compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league's Eastern Conference Southeast Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/miami_heat.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Los Angelese Lakers</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Los Angeles Lakers are an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles. The Lakers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league's Western Conference in the Pacific Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/los_angelese_lakers.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Minnesota Timberwolves</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Minnesota Timberwolves (also commonly known as the Wolves) are an American professional basketball team based in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The Timberwolves compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league's Western Conference Northwest Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/minnesota_timberwolves.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Oklahoma City Thunder</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Oklahoma City Thunder are an American professional basketball team based in Oklahoma City. The Thunder compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league's Western Conference Northwest Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/oklahomba_city_thunder.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Houston Rockets</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Houston Rockets are an American professional basketball team based in Houston, Texas. The Rockets compete in he National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league's Western Conference Southwest Division. </column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/houston_rockets.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Golden State Warriors</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Golden State Warriors are an American professional basketball team based in San Francisco. The Warriors compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA), as a member of the league's Western Conference Pacific Division. Founded in 1946 in Philadelphia.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/golden_state_warriors.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Cleveland Cavaliers</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Cleveland Cavaliers, often referred to as the Cavs, are an American professional basketball team based in Cleveland, Ohio. The Cavs compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league's Eastern Conference Central Division. </column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/cleveland_caveliers.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Chicago Bulls</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Chicago Bulls are an American professional basketball team based in Chicago, Illinois. The Bulls compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member of the league's Eastern Conference Central Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/chicago_bulls.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Indiana Pacers</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Indiana Pacers are an American professional basketball team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. The Pacers compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league's Eastern Conference Central Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/indiana_pacers.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Toronto Raptors</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Toronto Raptors are a Canadian professional basketball team based in Toronto, Ontario. The Raptors compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league's Eastern Conference Atlantic Division.</column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/toronto_raptors.jpg</column>
        </table>
        <table name="basketball_teams_website">
            <column name="team_name">Utah Jazz</column>
            <column name="team_description">The Utah Jazz are an American professional basketball team based in Salt Lake City, Utah. The Jazz compete in the National Basketball Association (NBA) as a member club of the league's Western Conference, Northwest Division. </column>
            <column name="image_link">../images/utah_jazz.png</column>
        </table>
    </database>
</pma_xml_export>